真的有这么明显吗？
Is it really that obvious?
我日日夜夜盯著你，因为
I've been eying you day and night, because
你看我的模样，就是我想要的
you look at me the way I want you to
而每天我都，中、中、中，中你计
And every day I fall, fall, fall for you
我们用同一艘船
And we're in the same boat
从没有到全都
from nothing to everything
这就是不同种的魔法
And it's a different kind of magic
不同种的人生体验
A different kind of life to live
我们真的有区别？
Are we all that different?
真的没区别？
Are we much the same?
还在寻找那个能够修好我们的人
And we're looking for somepony to make us whole again
我知道你是我的星光
And I know that you're my Starlight
魔法在我身边
The magic to all I am
请不要，问我过如何
Please don't ask how my day was
诚实会搞砸一切
Sincerity would fail me
还是喜欢把戏，拿下帽子就在
Still like to play tricks right outta the hat
你就别在意，让我说说我到底什么意思
Don't think about it, please just let me show you what I mean
每一天，我们都在找寻自我
Every day's a search for who we are
何时能喘口气
When will we catch a break
并欣然接受自己？
And be happy with who we are?
这就是不同种的魔法
And it's a different kind of magic
不同种的人生体验
A different kind of life to live
我们真的有区别？
Are we all that different?
真的没区别？
Are we much the same?
还在寻找那个能够修好我们的人
And we're looking for somepony to make us whole again
我知道你是我的星光
And I know that you're my Starlight
魔法在我身边
The magic to all I am
这就是不同种的魔法
And it's a different kind of magic
不同种的人生体验
A different kind of life to live
我们真的有区别？
Are we all that different?
真的没区别？
Are we much the same?
还在寻找那个能够修好我们的人...
And we're looking for somepony to make us whole again...